<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" version="2.0"><channel><title><![CDATA[Extended Night Companion]]></title><description><![CDATA[Home for information about the Extended Night Companion App, a mobile for the video game The Long Dark®]]></description><link>https://extendednightcompanion.com</link><generator>GatsbyJS</generator><lastBuildDate>Mon, 26 Apr 2021 19:07:11 GMT</lastBuildDate><item><title><![CDATA[Version 1.0.11]]></title><description><![CDATA[New Additions New Transition Zone Maps (The Ravine, Old Island Connector, etc.) New Cave Maps (No.3 Coal Mine, Gold Mine, etc.) Cairn Maps…]]></description><link>https://extendednightcompanion.com/v1.0.11/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://extendednightcompanion.com/v1.0.11/</guid><pubDate>Mon, 05 Apr 2021 22:12:03 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;h2&gt;New Additions&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;New Transition Zone Maps (The Ravine, Old Island Connector, etc.)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;New Cave Maps (No.3 Coal Mine, Gold Mine, etc.)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Cairn Maps&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Missing trophy data (Darkwalker Challenge, Event Badges, and Feats)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Analytics&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;h2&gt;What’s Next?&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;ol&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Items&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Journal&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ol&gt;
&lt;h2&gt;Notes&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;h3&gt;New “Buy me a coffee” site&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I have created a &lt;a href=&quot;https://ko-fi.com/brooksbecton&quot;&gt;“Buy me a coffee”&lt;/a&gt; site for those that have been asking if they can donate. Please do not feel like you are required to do so. To be clear, donating will not remove the ads in the app. &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h3&gt;In app purchase to remove ads&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I looked more into the possibility of adding the option to pay to remove ads within the app. There is a limitation with the technology I am using called Expo. Expo helps me develop features more quickly, but doesn’t currently support In App Purchases (IAP). They may in the future.  &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;You are required to use Apple or Google’s tools for IAP or risk getting your app removed if you try to go around it. &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;There are ways to transition away from using Expo and I plan on doing this after adding the items, journaling, and maybe the backpack features. &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h3&gt;Analytic Tools&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I’ve added a some tools to help me understand how people are using the app. Because of this there is a new link in the app’s &lt;a href=&quot;/privacy&quot;&gt;privacy policy&lt;/a&gt; and &lt;a href=&quot;/termsandconditions&quot;&gt;terms&lt;/a&gt; that links to that tools privacy policy and terms. Here are the links to their info &lt;a href=&quot;https://firebase.google.com/policies/analytics&quot;&gt;Google Analytics for Firebase Use Policy&lt;/a&gt; and &lt;a href=&quot;https://firebase.google.com/terms/analytics&quot;&gt;Google Analytics for Firebase Terms of Service&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2&gt;Thank You&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I am still having so much fun devloping the app and appreciate everyone’s support and feedback. &lt;/p&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Version 1.0.10]]></title><description><![CDATA[New Additions Colored maps for Timberwolf Mountain, Ash Canyon, and Hushed River Valley Custom Trophies Trophy Tabs  to hide completed…]]></description><link>https://extendednightcompanion.com/v1.0.10/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://extendednightcompanion.com/v1.0.10/</guid><pubDate>Tue, 23 Mar 2021 22:12:03 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;h2&gt;New Additions&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Colored maps for Timberwolf Mountain, Ash Canyon, and Hushed River Valley&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Custom Trophies&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Trophy Tabs  to hide completed trophies&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;New Change Log Screen&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Other various improvements&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;h2&gt;What’s Next?&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;ol&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Transition Zone Maps (Ravine, Crumbling Highway, etc.)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Remove Ads Option&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Items&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Journal&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ol&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I’ve created a short (~2-3 minute) to guage interest on a few things. &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://docs.google.com/forms/d/e/1FAIpQLSeHVUMfiYsybNZMK3viHRDdNWo4OaHUk8rjsks8RffTpkqvvQ/viewform?usp=sf_link&quot;&gt;Take the Survey!&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2&gt;Notes&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;There should be no more issues installing to any region/country with the app. I have seen that people are able to install from countries that could not previously. &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;There has been a few questions about adding/removing layers from the maps, such as, only showing wolfs areas or hide other things. Unfortunately, this won’t be possible right now. I’m using the maps directly from &lt;a href=&quot;https://steamcommunity.com/sharedfiles/filedetails/?id=1901570789&quot;&gt;this forum post&lt;/a&gt;. These maps are amazing, but they are just flat images. This idea is very good and is typical in most map applications. I will continue to think about this and try to figure out how this could work.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2&gt;Thank You&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;This has been such an exciting project for me and I am so excited to have support from the community. Thank you all.&lt;/p&gt;</content:encoded></item></channel></rss>